(upbeat funk pop music)
You know, I was, I was
wondering, you know,
if you could keep on,
because the force, it's got a lot of power
and it makes me feel like, ah,
it makes me feel like, ah,
Whoo!
♪ Lovely is the feelin' now ♪
♪ Fever, temperatures risin' now ♪
♪ Power (oh power) is the force, the vow ♪
♪ That makes it happen, it
asks no questions why (ooh) ♪
♪ So get closer (closer now) ♪
♪ To my body now ♪
♪ Just love me ♪
♪ 'Til you don't know how (ooh) ♪
♪ Keep on, with the force, don't stop ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you get enough ♪
♪ Touch me and I feel on fire ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' like a love desire (ooh) ♪
♪ I'm melting (I'm melting) ♪
♪ Like hot candle wax ♪
♪ Sensation (oh sensation) ♪
♪ Lovely where we're at (ooh) ♪
♪ So let love take us through the hours ♪
♪ I won't be complainin' (ooh) ♪
♪ 'Cause this is love power (ooh) ♪
♪ Keep on, with the force, don't stop ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you get enough ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ Lovely is the feeling now ♪
♪ I won't be complainin' (ooh ooh) ♪
♪ The force is love power ♪
♪ Keep on, with the force, don't stop ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you get enough ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you
get enough (oh girl) ♪
♪ Keep on, with the force, don't stop ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you get enough ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you get enough
('til you get enough, now) ♪
♪ Keep on, with the force, don't stop ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you get enough (ooh) ♪
♪ Keep on, with the
force, don't stop (yeah) ♪
♪ Don't stop 'til you get
enough (keep on baby) ♪
enough ('til you get enough) ♪
(funk pop music fading)